[{"answer": "I think it's more likely now that we'll have some debt ceiling and some CR conversation.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Or has everything moved to now a debt ceiling debate which will be resolved around that deadline?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes, I think that's very accurate.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Is that your understanding of how it went?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, it's heart-wrenching when a loved one is lost either way.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "I mean it's frankly sickening, isn't it?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Well, we are actually very hopeful that this is actual negotiating time.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "What were the strategy be from the Republicans to get through this on path that is now causing such havoc to so many Americans?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Look, at first, I'm not going to criticize John Boehner.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Has he misplayed his hand here?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "But look at, we've never had -- we never had to do that but, you know, we had ...", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Right, but let me ask you in all the eight years that you were the Speaker, were you ever in a position where you even contemplated forcing a government shutdown because you didn't agree with an established law?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, it depends on what the law was and it depends on what kind of support you had with your -- from your parties.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Would you have consider it though?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Under those circumstances could you imagine using that trying to defund that or make it somehow not happen as a stick to shut down the government?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Yes, you just made the argument.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "I don't think knowing my history of you, you would've done?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "... have died, yeah, as of right now, 26 people died since the shutdown, started.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Is it 26 as of today now?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Unfortunately, you know, we talked about this on one of the previous visits when I was here.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "How do you resolve what seems to be such an implacable divide between these two parties?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "I think we're very close to a deal and that's one of the reasons Obama is meeting with all the members in both parties of both Houses.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Did you see that as the way through all of this?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the Republican Party is beginning not only to look at the polls and see that they are digging themselves a deeper and deeper a hole and of course when you're digging a deep hole you don't want to continue to dig.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "It's pretty scandalous, isn't it?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "No, of course not.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Does a failure to deal with the debt ceiling on that particular day when it comes up, does that automatically calls America to default?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I have given the Larry Kudlow the last word but the good news is you can come back other -- tomorrow or the next day and have another word.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "You're giving Larry Kudlow the last word?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "When you look back to that day, you think back that day and you've obviously have to recall it all for your book, did anything at all warned you that he could possibly be capable of this -- the man you knew as you husband and a loving father of anything like this?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I really had no idea.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "What did you think was happening?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "You know, in the very first moment that afternoon, I knew that I was faced with two choices.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "I mean how did you find it?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "You know, I have.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Have you forgiven Charlie?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Did you hate him to start with?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Do you think it was depression over the loss of your little girl or you think it's a much more complicated situation?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "You know it's a really hard thing for me to see that and have minds months and even years after.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Even when you're described that way, did you worry that's the rest of your life that's how you'll going to be labeled now as the Amish Mass Shooters widow?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "ONVILLE: You know I knew that they needed to know all the details of that before they went back to school even that first week.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "How have you dealt with that?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "You know I think there are a lot of emotions wrapped up in that.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Did they feel angry towards him for what he did, not just those poor young girls but also to his own family?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Well, it takes me back to that moment and my heart breaks for everyone involved in those situations.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "What goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I mean, you know, Charlie had always enjoyed hunting and that was something that he did with his dad and the guns were locked at his parents home in a safe.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "He has -- We had an array of firearms on him, do you think it's too easy of people who have mental illness to get their hands on killing machines?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "You know I think that it's hard to keep them out of their hands if that's so their choice.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "You think it's too easy to get guns that given there were millions of people in America that have a form of mental illness?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "You found love again?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "You know I knew that if I wanted to have a relationship that was vibrant and alive with my husband Dan that I couldn't drag the past into my future that there was no future in the past.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "How difficult was it for you to trust a man after what had happened to you?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Yes I have.", "docId": "131009pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "ORGAN: Did you ever meet any of the families of the girls in the schools?", "qSentId": 507}]